CARLA HALL

<u>miss.hc3@gmail.com</u> 770-733-4750

SUMMARY:

I'm a seasoned sales professional with dynamic marketing, media training, regional management and account management experience. I have extensive experience developing new business, while cultivating existing client relationship and for long term retention. I empower growth development and management strategies; capable of leading and training. Well versed in strong presentation, negotiation, and communication skills; expert at building top-producing relationships with customers and business partners nationwide. Overall I'm a team player who is motivated and driven to help organizations succeed.

SALES PROFILE:

- > SaaS, EMR, E.H.R., LIS, PMS, CRM, SSI, API, FTP, ASP and Cloud hosted solution experience
- > Strong hunter business development mentality with the ability to foster growth in existing accounts
- > Consistent at delivering forecast that yield profitable sales
- Anatomical Pathology, Molecular Diagnostic and Therapeutic Biological Lab Testing Sales into Multiple Specialties
- LIS-Lab Information Systems, EMR- Electronic Medical Records and PMS-Practice Management System expertise
- Strong Business Development & Account Management Expertise
- > Full System Implementation Life Cycle Experience
- > Development of Business Partner Relationship/Project Management
- Sales Presentation & Contract Price Negotiation
- > Self-motivated, hardworking and aggressively consistent at closing long term business
- > Well Organized, Deadline Driven & Customer Focused

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Software: Windows Office Professional, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Desktop Publisher, Novell-GroupWise, SharePoint, Mac Office, WebEx and Microsoft Live Meeting

CRM Solutions: ACT software, Goldmine, Salesforce.com, Microsoft Dynamics, NetSuite, Sage CRM and Sales Logix

SALES TRAINING: Dialogue Sales, Integrity Selling, Dale Carnegie, Enterprise Sales Strategies, Spin Selling, Consultative Selling Techniques and Challenger Sales Methodology

EDUCATION:

Western Pennsylvania College of Health- Pittsburgh, PA-- Nursing

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

Branding Consultant - Ziv Empire, LLC -

1-2012 - 7-2014

Provide Healthcare prospects and clients with unique insight and expertise to strengthen their brand. Offer strategic planning to assist with development within diverse markets for branding and promotions and unified collaboration. Helping businesses develop brand awareness and expand their market share.

- Consult with Healthcare business across multiple cultural environments
- Present unique branding and marketing strategies that can provide national & international exposure
- Offer resources to help break through barriers that will advance their brand methodology
- Extend short-term and long-term roadmap plans

(Company closed)

<u>Area Sales Manager</u> – CompuGroup Medical

1-2011-2011

Area Sales Manager for LIS-Lab Information Systems and EMR-Electronic Medical Records systems. I covered 6 states implementing new business into hospitals and large clinics. I worked closely with vendor business partner representatives providing product presentations and helping them fully understand Compugroup Medical products and services. I provided full training and understanding of pricing, contracts, and delivery methods to help increase company profit margins.

- Develop new business within assigned territory
- Sales presentations to prospects and existing LIS, PMS & EMR customers
- Provided education on new products, services and product upgrades
- Helped develop business partnership relationships to advance Compugroup products
- Developed weekly and monthly forecast reports for VP of Sales
- Provide accurate and timely pipeline reporting into Sales Force.com
- Attend Regional and National Tradeshows
- Maintain effective communication with various internal departments, LIS & EMR Project Managers and partnership companies.

(Major company downsize after the purchased (8) US companies)

Regional Account Executive- LabCorp Tucker GA

2006-2010

Territory sales developing new business with Hospitals, Clinics, Physician Offices, Ambulatory Surgical Centers, Medical Universities, Ac ute Care/Skilled Care Facilities and State Prison Hospitals. Provide LabCorp's LIS-Lab Information System technology as the first line of new business service, to enable EDI interfacing with medical organizations mainframe systems. Promoting full service Clinical Pathology, Genomic Esoteric Testing, Cytology, Histology, Hematology, Immunology, Molecular, Biology, Anatomic Pathology, Neuropathology, Microbiology and a wide compendium of other specialty lab test. Worked with a number of lab test manufacture executives and LabCorp subsidiary companies such as Dianon, Monogram-HIV, Genzyme, Genetics & Oncology, Life Science, Hologic, Qiagen, Liposcience, Litholink, Diabetes, Kidney Disease, OTS Pain Management, Point of Care Drug testing, Relay Health, Dr. First etc... Present Clinical Trials options to help healthcare organizations accrue additional revenue. Delivery powerful onsite in-services and presentations, provide existing clients with a full understanding of lab test usage, EMR, PMS and LIS integration options. Discussed with clients their Fee Schedules, Lab billing ICD-9 and CPT codes for commercial insurance plans and Medical and Medicaid plans to facilitate proper monthly lab test billing.

- Provide new and existing prospects with wide compendium of Lab test solutions
- Worked with Physicians, PA's, Nurse Practitioners, RN's MA's, Lab Tech's Lab Managers, Clinic and Office Managers, Billing Managers, Administrators, CEO's and CIO's
- I worked with a large number of business partner companies, helping them implement LabCorp products and services into client's offices.
- Provided a comprehensive understanding of LabCorp solutions to business partners, pricing, products, services, usages, and ICD-9 and CPT codes for reimbursement.

Sales Representative-Sage Software, Duluth GA

2003-2005

Provide sales and marketing of CMR, Accounting, Payroll solutions to mid-market B2B. Identify the most effective software that best suits the client's business needs.

- New sales to prospects and up sales to existing clients
- Daily follow-up to new and pre-existing clients
- Presentations to decision makers on Sage CRM, Sales Logix, Medical Manager, Intergy EHR and HealthPro

Regional Sales Manager - Health Logic, Atlanta GA

2001-2003

Sales Management for a Medical Clearinghouse, I was responsible for 5 outside reps and 5 inside sales rep. Managed business operations and sales management; facilitated effective training and led the implementation of business solutions in compliance with company objectives. Analyzed and developed weekly and monthly work plans based on projected sale. I conducted weekly conference calls with reps. I worked closely with the VP of Sales, to capture revenue within untapped markets.

- Creating spreadsheet and flow charts to assist staff
- Conducted weekly conference calls and ride along with Reps
- Provided in-services to demo product for large Billing departments, IT and CFO's
- Develop training tools, coached, motivated and provided staff with expected sale goals

Early Positions:

WebMD/Emdeon: (Project Manager - Sales Executive) 1999-2001

Emory Hospital: (Managed Care Utilization Nurse) 1997 -1999